Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- China College Files, Series IV
  - Ginling College
    - Correspondence
      - Gundlach, Adelaide, 1938-1948 (Box 137, Folder 2753)
      - Gwan Dzun-sien, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 2753)
      - Hackett, Martha, 1936-1940 (Box 137, Folder 2753)
      - Haight, Edith, 1937-1948 (Box 137, Folder 2753)
      - Hall, Christine H., 1940 (Box 137, Folder 2754)
      - Harvard-Yenching Institute, 1929 (Box 137, Folder 2754)
      - Highbaugh, Irma, 1939-1941 (Box 137, Folder 2754)
      - Ho I-djen, 1930-1939 (Box 137, Folder 2754)
      - Ho Yung-djen, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 2754)
      - Hoffsommer, Abigail, 1936-1937 (Box 137, Folder 2755)
      - Hoh, Phoebe Y.T., 1927-1945 (Box 137, Folder 2756)
      - Hoskins, Mrs. Harold B., 1940 (Box 137, Folder 2756)
      - Hsi Mo-chuen, 1945 (Box 137, Folder 2756)
      - Hsiung Gueh-djen, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 2756)
      - Hsiung Ya-na, 1945-1947 (Box 137, Folder 2757)
      - Hsu Ya-fen, 1931-1940 (Box 137, Folder 2757)
      - Hu Shih, 1940 (Box 137, Folder 2757)
      - Hu Shih-tsang, 1945-1947 (Box 137, Folder 2757)
      - Hu Siu-ying, 1945-1948 (Box 137, Folder 2757)
      - Hung Dah-ling, 1944 (Box 137, Folder 2758)
      - Hutchison Memorial, 1943 (Box 137, Folder 2758)
      - Hwang Chia-yu, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 2758)
      - Hwang Dju, 1946 (Box 137, Folder 2758)
      - Hwang, Dzun-mei, 1939 (Box 137, Folder 2758)
      - Hwang Li-ming, 1933-1941 (Box 137, Folder 2759)
      - Hwang Nan, 1946 (Box 137, Folder 2759)
      - Hwang Wen-yu, 1935 (Box 137, Folder 2759)
      - Hwang Yen-hwa, 1946 (Box 137, Folder 2759)
      - Hwang Yin-shi, 1943 (Box 137, Folder 2759)
      - Hwang Yu-chang, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 2760)
      - Hwang Yu-tsuen, 1945 (Box 137, Folder 2760)
      - Jarvis, Anna, 1945 (Box 137, Folder 2760)
      - Kalamazoo College Women's League, 1940-1948 (Box 137, Folder 2760)
      - Kao Ling-ying, 1946 (Box 137, Folder 2760)
      - Kirk, Florence, 1932-1948 (Box 138, Folder 2761-2765)
      - Kirk, Lillian, 1939-1946 (Box 138, Folder 2766)
      - Koo, Ellen Y.T., 1927 (Box 138, Folder 2767)
      - Kwoh Sih-ung, 1945-1947 (Box 138, Folder 2767)
      - Lai Shuh-ying, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 2767)
      - Lan Chien-wei, 1938 (Box 138, Folder 2767)
      - Leiper, Eleanor C., 1932 (Box 138, Folder 2767)
      - Li Cheng-lan, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 2767)
      - Koo, Elien Y.T., 1927 (Box 138, Folder 2767)
      - Li Chi, 1949 (Box 138, Folder 2768)
      - Li Djoh-i, 1937-1939 (Box 138, Folder 2768)
      - Li Dze-djen, 1930-1945 (Box 138, Folder 2768)
      - Li Gwan-yuen, 1943 (Box 138, Folder 2768)
      - Li Han-fen, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 2768)
      - Li Man-kuei, 1940 (Box 138, Folder 2769)
      - Li Mei-yun, 1940-1944 (Box 138, Folder 2769)
      - Li Ming-dju, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 2769)
      - Li Tien-lu, 1940 (Box 138, Folder 2769)
      - Lin Chung-djih, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 2770)
      - Lin Deh-djih, 1930 (Box 138, Folder 2770)
      - Lin Dji-yu, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 2770)
      - Lin Pei-feng, 1945-1949 (Box 138, Folder 2770)
      - Lin Yu-wen, 1937 (Box 138, Folder 2771)
      - Lin Yueh-dwen, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 2771)
      - Lindbergh, Anne M. (copy of check), 1941 (Box 138, Folder 2771)
      - Liu Bao-ying, 1938 (Box 138, Folder 2772)
      - Liu Chao-ko, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 2772)
      - Liu Ching-ho, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 2772)
      - Liu En-lan, 1927-1948 (Box 138, Folder 2773)
      - Liu Gien-tsui, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 2774)
      - Liu Hsi-meng, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 2774)
      - Liu Kai-yung, 1940-1945 (Box 138, Folder 2774)
      - Liu, Mary, 1946 (Box 138, Folder 2774)
      - Liu Mi-cio, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 2774)
      - Liu Siu-an, 1928-1929 (Box 139, Folder 2775)
      - Liu Yu-hsia, 1936-1938 (Box 139, Folder 2775)
      - Liu Yung-szi, 1947 (Box 139, Folder 2775)
      - Lo Ai-djen, 1940-1945 (Box 139, Folder 2775)
      - Lobenstine, Edwin C., 1937-1945 (Box 139, Folder 2776)
      - Loh, Homer C., 1946 (Box 139, Folder 2776)
      - Loomis, Helen M., 1932-1935 (Box 139, Folder 2776)
      - Lu Gwei-djen, 1934-1947 (Box 139, Folder 2777)
      - Lu Mei-ying, 1937-1940 (Box 139, Folder 2777)
      - Lu Shuh-chin, 1945 (Box 139, Folder 2777)
      - Lu Shuh-ying, 1932, 1948 (Box 139, Folder 2777)
      - Luce, Henry W., 1937 (Box 139, Folder 2778)
      - Luh Ging-wei, 1945-1947 (Box 139, Folder 2778)
      - Luh Sin-tsing, 1947 (Box 139, Folder 2778)
      - Luh Tsung, 1938 (Box 139, Folder 2778)
      - Lui An-mei, 1947 (Box 139, Folder 2778)
      - Ma Teh-yin, 1942-1946 (Box 139, Folder 2779)
      - McAfee, Cleland Boyd, 1940 (Box 139, Folder 2779)
      - McClelland, Mr. and Mrs. Robert, 1945 (Box 139, Folder 2779)
      - McCoy, Helen, 1936-1948 (Box 139, Folder 2779)
      - McCurdy, Eleanor, 1948 (Box 139, Folder 2779)
      - MacKenzie, Rachel, 1940 (Box 139, Folder 2780)
      - Macmillan, Eva, 1935-1941 (Box 139, Folder 2780)
      - McNair, Harley F., 1938 (Box 139, Folder 2780)
      - Mao Shwen-yu, 1927 (Box 139, Folder 2780)
      - Mao Yun-man, 1946 (Box 139, Folder 2780)
      - Mead, Frederica, 1920,1936-1947 (Box 139, Folder 2781)
      - Mei, Mrs. Y.P., 1939 (Box 139, Folder 2781)
      - Merrow, Llewella, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 2781)
      - Methodist Episcopal Church, South, 1920-1936 (Box 139, Folder 2782)
      - Meyer, Harriet Cogswell, 1943-1945 (Box 139, Folder 2782)
      - Michigan University, 1941-1946 (Box 139, Folder 2783)
      - Milam, Ava B., 1936-1944 (Box 139, Folder 2783)
      - Moffet, Anna, 1930-1937 (Box 139, Folder 2783)
      - Moo Tsing, 1945 (Box 139, Folder 2784)
      - Moore, Elisabeth Luce, 1942 (Box 139, Folder 2784)
      - Morris, Alice E., 1945 (Box 139, Folder 2784)
      - Morrow, Elizabeth C., 1927-1943 (Box 139, Folder 2784)
      - Mossman, Mereb, 1930-1945 (Box 139, Folder 2785-2788)
      - Mott, John R., 1936 (Box 139, Folder 2789)
      - Munger, Jessie, 1936-1937 (Box 139, Folder 2789)
      - New, Mrs. Way-sung, 1936-1947 (Box 139, Folder 2790-2794)
      - New York State Department of Education, 1918-1938 (Box 140, Folder 2795-2796)
      - Nien Yi-tao Rest House, 1937-1938 (Box 140, Folder 2797)
      - Niu Yu-hwa, 1944-1946 (Box 140, Folder 2797)
      - Nourse, Mary A., 1937-1941 (Box 140, Folder 2797)
      - Ong Hwei-lan, 1934-1947 (Box 140, Folder 2798)
      - Owens, Katharine Greene, 1948-1949 (Box 140, Folder 2799)
      - Pan Ren-tsiu, 1947 (Box 140, Folder 2799)
      - Pan Yao-tsien, 1945-1948 (Box 140, Folder 2799)
      - Peabody, Mrs. Henry, 1940 (Box 140, Folder 2800)
      - Pedersen, Esther, 1940 (Box 140, Folder 2800)
      - Peng, Mrs. C.L., 1937 (Box 140, Folder 2800)
      - Peng Shuh-chuan, 1947 (Box 140, Folder 2800)
      - Plaum, Helen M., 1946-1948 (Box 140, Folder 2801)
      - Porter, Caroline J., 1943-1947 (Box 140, Folder 2802)
      - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Board of Foreign Missions, 1931-1935 (Box 140, Folder 2803)
      - Priest, Elsie, 1931-1939 (Box 140, Folder 2804)
      - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1928-1948 (Box 140, Folder 2805)
      - Quon, Lily Ho, 1937-1945 (Box 140, Folder 2806)
      - Ran Lung-Shuh, 1947 (Box 140, Folder 2806)
      - Rathbone, Josephine, 1943 (Box 140, Folder 2806)
      - Rawles, Katharine R., 1936-1938 (Box 140, Folder 2806)
      - Reardon, Nina, 1940-1941 (Box 140, Folder 2806)
      - Reeves, Cora, 1917-1948 (Box 140, Folder 2807-2809)
      - Rhead, Mabel R., 1936-1947 (Box 140, Folder 2810)
      - Rhodes, Esther, 1937-1943 (Box 141, Folder 2811)
      - Robertson, Leila, 1937-1939 (Box 141, Folder 2812)
      - Rohrman Fund, 1932 (Box 141, Folder 2812)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1943 (Box 141, Folder 2812)
      - Rounds, Alice Darrow, 1940 (Box 141, Folder 2813)
      - Sage, Pauline, 1938-1940 (Box 141, Folder 2813)
      - Sarvis, Maude L., 1940 (Box 141, Folder 2813)
      - Schutze, Katherine, 1940-1948 (Box 141, Folder 2813)
      - Settlemeyer, Alice, 1940-1945 (Box 141, Folder 2814)
      - Shao Ih-deh, 1947 (Box 141, Folder 2814)
      - Shao Siu-lin, 1937-1940 (Box 141, Folder 2814)
      - Sharp, Gratia, 1929-1943 (Box 141, Folder 2815)
      - Shen Dzu-ying, 1939 (Box 141, Folder 2815)
      - Shepherd, George W., 1937 (Box 141, Folder 2815)
      - Shih, Pao-chen, 1938 (Box 141, Folder 2815)
      - Shipley, Mary Boyd, 1917-1940 (Box 141, Folder 2816)
      - Shipman, Julia, 1937-1938 (Box 141, Folder 2816)
      - Shippen, Ellen F., 1940 (Box 141, Folder 2816)
      - Shoup, Louise, 1936-1947 (Box 141, Folder 2817)
      - Siao Ding-ying, 1939 (Box 141, Folder 2817)
      - Sie Hsieh-shuh, 1947 (Box 141, Folder 2817)
      - Sie Hsien-gieh, 1945-1946 (Box 141, Folder 2817)
      - Smith College Alumnae Association, 1937-1951 (Box 141, Folder 2818-2824)
      - Smith College Faculty, 1935-1944 (Box 142, Folder 2825)
      - Smith, Elizabeth, 1949 (Box 142, Folder 2826)
      - Smithwick, Gladys, 1947 (Box 142, Folder 2826)
      - Spicer, Eva, 1932-1948 (Box 142, Folder 2827-2829)
      - Sprague, Florence, 1937-1945 (Box 142, Folder 2830)
      - Starn, Pauline, 1943-1945 (Box 142, Folder 2830)
      - Steele, Mary E., 1948 (Box 142, Folder 2830)
      - Stendel, Dorothy, 1940 (Box 142, Folder 2830)
      - Sueh Deh-yu, 1947 (Box 142, Folder 2831)
      - Sun, Mrs. J.H., 1938 (Box 142, Folder 2831)
      - Sung, Ai-li, 1942 (Box 142, Folder 2831)
      - Sutherland, Catharine, 1926-1947 (Box 142, Folder 2832-2836)
      - Swain, Leslie E., 1937 (Box 142, Folder 2837)
      - Sweeny, Mary E., 1939-1943 (Box 142, Folder 2837)
      - Sweet Briar College, 1947-1948 (Box 142, Folder 2837)
      - Swen En-lien, 1946-1947 (Box 142, Folder 2837)
      - Swen Ming-ching, Mr. and Mrs., 1939-1947 (Box 142, Folder 2837)
      - Swen Ta-shuen, 1946 (Box 142, Folder 2838)
      - Swen Yen-djen, 1947 (Box 142, Folder 2838)
      - Tang In-wen, 1946 (Box 142, Folder 2838)
      - Tang Mingsin (Box 142, Folder 2838)
      - Tao Shan-ming, 1936-1941 (Box 142, Folder 2838)
      - Tappert, Esther E., 1929-1945 (Box 142, Folder 2839)
      - Teagle, Mrs. Frank H., 1940-1941 (Box 142, Folder 2840)
      - Teng, Mrs. Chia-tun, 1939 (Box 142, Folder 2840)
      - Thayer, Mary V., 1940 (Box 142, Folder 2840)
      - Thomas Memorial Book Fund, 1936 (Box 142, Folder 2840)
      - Thompson, Margaret, 1937 (Box 142, Folder 2841)
      - Thomson, Margaret Cook, 1936-1940 (Box 142, Folder 2841)
      - Thurston, Matilda Calder, 1913-1947 (Box 143, Folder 2842-2853)
      - Thurston, Matilda Calder (Edited letters, pp. 1-216), 1913-1919 (Box 143A, Folder 2854-2855)
      - Thurston, Matilda Calder (Edited letters, 1-362), 1921-1927 (Box 144, Folder 2856-2857)
      - Thurston, Matilda Calder (Edited letters, pp. 1-240), 1928-1929 (Box 144, Folder 2858-2860)
      - Thurston, Matilda Calder (Edited letters, pp. 1-247), 1930-1934 (Box 144, Folder 2861-2862)
      - Treudley, Mary B., 1927-1941 (Box 144, Folder 2863)
      - Tsai Deh-sui, 1945 (Box 144, Folder 2864)
      - Tsai Dz-gu, 1944 (Box 144, Folder 2864)
      - Tsai Kwei, 1945 (Box 144, Folder 2864)
      - Tsang Tsai-i, 1947 (Box 144, Folder 2864)
      - Ts'en Su-hsing, 1946 (Box 144, Folder 2864)
      - Tseo Deh-shan, 1947 (Box 144, Folder 2865)
      - Tsiang, Mrs. T.F., 1945 (Box 144, Folder 2865)
      - Tsien, Lily, 1945-1946 (Box 144, Folder 2865)
      - Tsih Gi-lan, 1946 (Box 144, Folder 2865)
      - Tsiu, Mrs. S.F., 1945-1946 (Box 144, Folder 2865)
      - Tsou Te-fan, 1942 (Box 144, Folder 2866)
      - Tsu Yu-chi, 1934-1943 (Box 144, Folder 2866)
      - Tsui Deh-djen, 1947 (Box 144, Folder 2866)
      - Tsui Ya-lan, 1940 (Box 144, Folder 2866)
      - Tyler, Florence, 1932-1947 (Box 144, Folder 2867)
      - United China Relief, 1943 (Box 144, Folder 2867)
      - United Christian Missionary Society (Disciples of Christ), 1922-1948 (Box 144, Folder 2868)
      - Universalist Church, Association of Universalist Women, 1943-1948 (Box 145, Folder 2869)
      - Van Dusen, Henry P., 1939-1947 (Box 145, Folder 2870)
      - Van Kirk, Ruth, 1941-1945 (Box 145, Folder 2870)
      - Vautrin Memorial Fund, 1942 (Box 145, Folder 2870)
      - Vautrin, Minnie, 1919-1941 (Box 145, Folder 2871-2881)
      - Walker, Pearl L., 1944 (Box 146, Folder 2882)
      - Walmsley, Evelyn, 1936-1943 (Box 146, Folder 2882)
      - Wang An-chen, 1947 (Box 146, Folder 2883)
      - Wang Ming-chen, 1939-1943 (Box 146, Folder 2883)
      - Wang Shu-hsi, 1938 (Box 146, Folder 2883)
      - Wang Whei-ying, 1942 (Box 146, Folder 2883)
      - Wang Yin-ying, 1941 (Box 146, Folder 2884)
      - Wang Ying-an, 1944 (Box 146, Folder 2884)
      - Wang Yun-chieh, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 2884)
      - Werner, Emily, 1932-1938 (Box 146, Folder 2885)
      - Western College, Oxford, Ohio, 1944-1948 (Box 146, Folder 2886)
      - Whitmer, Harriet, 1923-1948 (Box 146, Folder 2887-2889)
      - Whitney, Edward S., 1949 (Box 146, Folder 2890)
      - Whittington, Dorothy and Harry, 1942-1948 (Box 146, Folder 2890)
      - Wild, Laura H., 1923-1946 (Box 146, Folder 2891)
      - Wilde, Almena Gray, 1938-1940 (Box 146, Folder 2891)
      - Wilson College, 1942-1948 (Box 146, Folder 2891)
      - Wilson, Helen B., 1936-1940 (Box 146, Folder 2892)
      - Wing, Adeline F., 1942 (Box 146, Folder 2892)
      - Winter, Etta F., 1943-1948 (Box 146, Folder 2892)
      - Woman's College Club of Saranac Lake and Lake Placid, 1944-1946 (Box 146, Folder 2892)
      - Wood, Norman A., 1940 (Box 146, Folder 2893)
      - Woolley, Mary E., 1940-1941 (Box 146, Folder 2893)
      - World Day of Prayer offerings, 1943-1947 (Box 146, Folder 2893)
      - Wu Bing-heng, 1947 (Box 146, Folder 2893)
      - Wu, Blanche, 1932-1948 (Box 146, Folder 2893)
      - Wu Deh-hwa, 1947 (Box 146, Folder 2894)
      - Wu Mao-i, 1939-1946 (Box 146, Folder 2894)
      - Wu Mei-lin, 1945-1947 (Box 146, Folder 2895)
      - Wu Suen-i, 1940-1946 (Box 146, Folder 2895)
      - Wu Yi-fang, 1927-1936 (Box 147, Folder 2896-2909)
      - Wu Yi-fang, 1937-1943 (Box 148, Folder 2910-2923)
      - Wu Yi-fang, 1944-1949,n.d. (Box 149, Folder 2924-2932)
      - Yang Ai-lien, 1945-1946 (Box 149, Folder 2933)
      - Yang, Alice, 1938 (Box 149, Folder 2933)
      - Yang, Ging-djung, 1945 (Box 149, Folder 2933)
      - Yang, Hwei-ru, 1938 (Box 149, Folder 2933)
      - Yang Hwei-ying, 1947 (Box 149, Folder 2934)
      - Yang, Li-ling, 1946 (Box 149, Folder 2934)
      - Yarnell, Adm. H.E., 1939 (Box 149, Folder 2934)
      - Yeh Dzing-wan, 1947 (Box 149, Folder 2934)
      - Yeh, Lucy Leng, 1940-1947 (Box 149, Folder 2935)
      - Yen Tsai-yun, 1933-1941 (Box 149, Folder 2936)
      - Ying, Mrs. S.T., 1937-1938 (Box 149, Folder 2936)
      - Yong, Soo, 1941 (Box 149, Folder 2936)
      - YWCA, 1931-1945 (Box 149, Folder 2936)
      - Yu Chih Shang-teh, 1940 (Box 149, Folder 2936)
      - Yu Hai-hsing, 1947 (Box 149, Folder 2937)
      - Yu Hsien-hsing, 1945 (Box 149, Folder 2937)
      - Yu Siu-ping, 1937-1938 (Box 149, Folder 2937)
      - Yuan Yen-ho, 1947 (Box 149, Folder 2938)
      - Yung Hsiao-yun, 1940 (Box 149, Folder 2938)
      - Zeta Tau Alpha Scholarship, 1944-1946 (Box 149, Folder 2938)
    - Financial Records
      - Transfer book, ca.1936-1951 (Box 150, Folder 2939)
      - Ledger, ca.1936-1957 (Box 150, Folder 2940)
      - Budgets, statements, 1936-1942, 1955 (Box 150, Folder 2941)
      - Record of donations, 1938, 1948 (Box 150, Folder 2942)
      - Record of donations, 1949-1951 (Box 151, Folder 2943-2944)
      - Special gifts, 1920-1936 (Box 151, Folder 2945)
    - Periodical Publications
      - The Pioneer, 1919 (Box 151, Folder 2946)
      - Ginling College Magazine, 1924-1929 (Box 151, Folder 2947-2950)
      - Ginling College Magazine, 1929-1930 (Box 152, Folder 2951)
      - Ginling College Letter, 1924-1926 (Box 152, Folder 2952)
      - Ginling College News Letter, 1934 (Box 152, Folder 2953)
      - Ginling News, 1942, 1945 (Box 152, Folder 2953)
      - Ginling Annual, 1932-1934 (Box 152, Folder 2954)
      - Ginling Annual, 1935, 1936 (Box 153, Folder 2955)
      - Ginling Association in America Newsletter, 1951-1973, 1977 (Box 154, Folder 2956-2961)
    - Publicity/reports
      - Annual and President's reports, 1916-1948 (Box 155, Folder 2962-2964)
      - Brochures, 1911-1941 (Box 155, Folder 2965-2972)
      - Brochures, 1942-1950 (Box 156, Folder 2973)
      - Chinese language pamphlets (Box 156, Folder 2974)
      - "Ginling Vignettes", 1917-1948 (Box 156, Folder 2975-2984)
      - Magazine Articles, 1935-1950,n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2985)
      - News letters, 1916-1938 Mar (Box 157, Folder 2986-2993)
      - News letters, 1938 Apr-1946 (Box 158, Folder 2994-3002)
      - News letters, 1947-1950, 1964 (Box 159, Folder 3003-3005)
      - News letters, fragments n.d. (Box 159, Folder 3006)
      - Material put out by Assoc. of Universalist Women, 1944-1948 (Box 159, Folder 3007)
      - Related to Rural Service Stations, 1939-1950 (Box 159, Folder 3008)
      - Photograph captions, 1938-1948,n.d. (Box 159, Folder 3009)
      - Appeals for donations, 1935-1949 (Box 159, Folder 3010)
      - Directed toward Smith College alumnae: Appeals for donations, 1937-1946 (Box 159, Folder 3011)
      - Directed toward Smith College alumnae, Ginling representatives, 1940-1951 (Box 159, Folder 3012)
      - Directed toward Smith College alumnae: Brochures, reports, 1937-1950 (Box 159, Folder 3013)
  - Hangchow Christian College (University)
    - Administrative
      - Board of Directors: Minutes and constitution, 1914-1950 (Box 160, Folder 3014)
      - Field Board of Control: Minutes, 1922-1938 (Box 160, Folder 3015, 3016)
      - Board of Trustees: Minutes, reports, 1939-1949 (Box 160, Folder 3017)
      - Hangchow University Committee of the UBCCC: Minutes, 1950, 1951 (Box 160, Folder 3018)
      - Re. cooperation between Hangchow and Soochow, 1941 (Box 160, Folder 3019)
      - Re. temporary campus in Shaowu, Fukien, 1942-1944 (Box 160, Folder 3020)
      - Hangchow University: Provisional Council, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 3021)
    - Academic
      - Catalogs, announcements, 1904-1944 (Box 160, Folder 3022-3024)
      - Student enrollment statistics, 1943-1949 (Box 160, Folder 3026)
      - Related to alumni, 1947-1956 (Box 160, Folder 3027)
      - Related to faculty members, 1947-1950, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 3028)
    - Correspondence
      - Lee, Baen E., 1933-1945 (Box 160, Folder 3029,3030)
      - March, Arthur W., 1944 (Box 160, Folder 3031)
      - McMullen, Robert J., 1937-1940 (Box 160, Folder 3032, 3033)
      - McMullen Robert J., 1941-1945 (Box 161, Folder 3034)
      - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., 1942-1945 (Box 161, Folder 3035)
      - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1932-1943 (Box 161, Folder 3036)
      - Scott, George T. (see also: Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.), 1938 (Box 161, Folder 3037)
    - Financial records
      - Financial records, 1936-1944, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 3038)
    - Periodical publications
      - Campus Life, 1930-1934 (Box 161, Folder 3039)
      - The Tide (yearbook), 1924-1926 (Box 161, Folder 3040)
    - Publicity/ reports
      - Annual reports, 1911-1931 (Box 162, Folder 3041, 3042)
      - Annual reports, 1936-1947 (Box 162, Folder 3043)
      - President's report, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 3043)
      - Brochures, 1905-c.a. 1948, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 3044, 3045)
      - Miscellaneous, 1912-1950 (Box 162, Folder 3046-3049)
  - Huachung (College) University
    - Administrative
      - Related to formation of Central China University, and predecessor, Boone University, 1921, 1928-1929 (Box 163, Folder 3050)
      - Constitution, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 3051)
      - Re. Charter, 1943 (Box 163, Folder 3051)
      - Correspondence related to incorporation of Board of Trustees, 1934-1935 (Box 163, Folder 3052)
      - Constitutions and By-laws:, 1943 (Box 163, Folder 3053)
      - Board of Trustees (known as Board of Founders), 1931-1947 (Box 163, Folder 3054-3057)
      - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee, 1935-1947 (Box 163, Folder 3058-3060)
      - Huachung Committee of the United Board, 1947-1957 (Box 163, Folder 3061-3063)
      - Central College Foundation, 1935-1946 (Box 164, Folder 3064)
      - Board of Directors: General, 1929, 1935-1937, 1948, 1950 (Box 164, Folder 3065)
      - Board of Directors: Executive Committee, 1938-1950 (Box 164, Folder 3066)
      - Board of Directors: Standing Committee, 1935 (Box 164, Folder 3067)
      - President's annual reports, 1931-1950 (Box 164, Folder 3068-3071)
      - Yale-in-China Board of Trustees, 1929, 1940, 1941, 1945 (Box 164, Folder 3072)
      - Blueprints and architectural drawings (Box 164, Folder 3073, 3074)
      - Re. property, 1935-1937 (Box 164, Folder 3075)
    - Academic
      - Catalogs, 1932, 1934-1936 (Box 165, Folder 3076, 3077)
      - Dean's reports, 1942-1948 (Box 165, Folder 3078)
      - Student enrollment statistics, 1939-1950 (Box 165, Folder 3079)
      - Alumni questionnaires, 1947 (Box 165, Folder 3080)
      - Related to faculty members, 1945-1950 (Box 165, Folder 3081)
      - Department of Chinese Literature and History, 1943-1948 (Box 165, Folder 3082)
      - School of Education, 1941-1947 (Box 165, Folder 3083)
      - School of Science, 1934-1948 (Box 165, Folder 3083)
      - Miscellaneous, incl. banner, 1940-1947,n.d. (Box 165, Folder 3084)
    - Correspondence
      - Anderson, David, 1939-1950 (Box 166, Folder 3085)
      - Beaver, R. Pierce, 1944-1948 (Box 166, Folder 3085)
      - Bergamini, Van Wie, 1938-1948 (Box 166, Folder 3085)
      - Bien, Richard P., 1945-1948 (Box 166, Folder 3086-3088)
      - Coe, John L., 1941-1946 Aug (Box 166, Folder 3089-3096)
      - Coe, John L., 1946 Sept-1947 (Box 167, Folder 3097, 3098)
      - Coe, John L., 1948-1949, 1958 (Box 167, Folder 3099)
      - Coe, Mary Richards, 1946-1948 (Box 167, Folder 3099)
      - Evangelical and Reformed Church, Board of International Missions, 1941-1948 (Box 167, Folder 3100)
      - Evangelical United Brethren Church, Department of World Missions, 1947 (Box 167, Folder 3101)
      - Foreign Missions Conference of North America, 1944-1945 (Box 167, Folder 3102)
      - Harvard-Yenching Institute, 1937-1944 (Box 167, Folder 3102)
      - Holmes Scholarship Fund, 1944 (Box 167, Folder 3103)
      - Hsiao, Sidney Chihti, 1941-1947 (Box 167, Folder 3103)
      - Hume, Edward H., 1923-1934, 1944 (Box 167, Folder 3104)
      - Hwang, Pu, 1937-1938 (Box 167, Folder 3104)
      - Johnston, Mary E., 1936-1944 (Box 167, Folder 3105)
      - Lo, John C.F. and Ruth Earnshaw, 1940-1950 (Box 167, Folder 3106,3107)
      - Lobenstine, Edwin C., 1937-1945 (Box 167, Folder 3108)
      - London Missionary Society, 1928-1947 (Box 167, Folder 3109)
      - Lyford, Oliver S., 1933-1941 (Box 167, Folder 3110-3112)
      - Lyford, Oliver S., 1942-1949 (Box 168, Folder 3113-3117)
      - Methodist Church, Board of Missions and Church Extension, 1944-1948 (Box 168, Folder 3118)
      - Methodist Episcopal Church, Board of Foreign Missions, 1933, 1934 (Box 168, Folder 3118)
      - Methodist Missionary Society, 1929-1948 (Box 168, Folder 3119)
      - Miller, Everard P., 1943 (Box 168, Folder 3120)
      - Moore, Dale H., 1947-1949 (Box 168, Folder 3120)
      - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1923-1949 (Box 168, Folder 3121, 3122)
      - Rank, Joseph Benevolent Trust, 1947-1948 (Box 168, Folder 3123)
      - Reformed Church in the U.S., 1939-1940 (Box 168, Folder 3123)
      - Roots, Logan H., Bp., 1928-1929 (Box 168, Folder 3124)
      - Sherman, Arthur M., 1928-1948 (Box 168, Folder 3125-3127)
      - Slater, Noel B., 1946 (Box 169, Folder 3128)
      - Wang, Donald Do-En, 1947 (Box 169, Folder 3128)
      - Ward, Paul L., 1946-1949 (Box 169, Folder 3129-3133)